<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC "-//APACHE//DTD Documentation V1.2//EN" "http://apache.org/forrest/dtd/document-v12.dtd">
<document>
  <header>
    <title>Apache MyFaces</title>
  </header>
  <body>
    <section>
      <title>Welcome to The MyFaces Project</title>
      <p>This is the official homepage of the first free open source JavaServer(tm) Faces implementation called "MyFaces".</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>What is JavaServer(tm) Faces?</title>
      <p>
      	JavaServer(tm) Faces is a new and upcoming web application framework that accomplishes the MVC paradigm.
      	 It is comparable to the well-known <link href="http://struts.apache.org/">Struts Framework</link> but has features and concepts that are beyond those of Struts.
Look at <link href="http://java.sun.com/j2ee/javaserverfaces/">Sun's JavaServer(tm) Page</link> to learn more about the <link href="http://www.jcp.org/en/jsr/detail?id=127">Java Specification Request 127</link> and to download the specification. They also provide a useful Tutorial there.

      </p>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>May 23, 2005 - Upcoming MyFaces sessions</title>
        <p>
            The MyFaces committers will be presenting their framework at <link href="http://java.sun.com/javaone/">JavaOne</link> 
            and also at <link href="http://apachecon.com/2005/EU/html/sessions.html">ApacheCon Europe</link>.
        </p>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>May 3, 2005 - MyFaces source code moves to Subversion</title>
        <p>
            The MyFaces source code has been moved from CVS to Subversion (SVN.)  This move will help us maintain the anticipated new MyFaces 
            subprojects.  It also bring us into compliance with the ASF goal of moving all CVS projects to SVN by the end of the year.  Click 
            <link href="community/versioning.html">here </link> for more details on how to access the source code.  
        </p>
    </section>
    
    <section>
        <title>April 16, 2005 - MyFaces 1.0.9(m9) has been released</title>
        <p>
            MyFaces 1.0.9(m9) is now available.  The (m9) stands for milestone 9.  The license agreement covering JSF and all other JCP based
            specifications require that we use this terminology and avoid the word "final."  Once MyFaces passes the TCK we will be able to
            refer to our releases as final.  This is one of the reasons why we initially pulled the release announcement from the website a
            few days ago.  But the release is official now and is available through your nearest Apache mirror.  Enjoy!
        </p>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>April 5, 2005 - MyFaces 1.0.9 RC3 now available</title>
        <p>
            MyFaces 1.0.9 RC3 is now available <link href="http://cvs.apache.org/builds/myfaces/release">here</link>.
            Please help us prepare for the official release by testing and providing feedback.  If you think you have found a
            bug, please report it <link href="http://issues.apache.org/jira/secure/BrowseProject.jspa?id=10600">here</link>.
        </p>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>April 1, 2005 - Nightly builds are now available</title>
        <p>
            Nightly builds are now available <link href="http://cvs.apache.org/builds/myfaces/nightly">here</link>.  Go ahead and download
            them if you wish to use the latest and greatest source code before the next official release.
        </p>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>Resources</title>
        <p>If you are new to JavaServer Faces Technology look at the following resources to become familar with JSF:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><link href="http://www.jsfcentral.com/">JSFCentral</link></li>
            <li><link href="http://www.jamesholmes.com/JavaServerFaces/">James Holmes' JSF Resources</link></li>
        </ul>
    </section>

  </body>
</document>
