<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE document PUBLIC "-//APACHE//DTD Documentation V1.2//EN" "http://apache.org/forrest/dtd/document-v12.dtd">
<document> 
  <header> 
    <title>Apache MyFaces</title> 
  </header> 
  <body> 
    <section>
      <title>Welcome to The MyFaces Project</title>
      <p>This is the official homepage of the first free open source JavaServer(tm) Faces implementation called "MyFaces".</p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title>What is JavaServer(tm) Faces?</title>
      <p>
      	JavaServer(tm) Faces is a new and upcoming web application framework that accomplishes the MVC paradigm.
      	 It is comparable to the well-known <link href="http://struts.apache.org/">Struts Framework</link> but has features and concepts that are beyond those of Struts.
Look at <link href="http://java.sun.com/j2ee/javaserverfaces/">Sun's JavaServer(tm) Page</link> to learn more about the <link href="http://www.jcp.org/en/jsr/detail?id=127">Java Specification Request 127</link> and to download the specification. They also provide a useful Tutorial there.
 	
      </p>
    </section>
	
    <section>
        <title>April 2, 2005 - Nightly builds are now available</title>
        <p>
            Nightly builds are now available <link href="http://cvs.apache.org/builds/myfaces/nightly">here</link>.  Go ahead and download  
            them if you wish to use the latest and greatest source code before the next official release.
        </p>
    </section>
    <section>
        <title>March 29, 2005 - MyFaces 1.0.9 RC2 now available</title>
        <p>
            My Faces 1.0.9 RC2 is now available <link href="http://cvs.apache.org/dist/myfaces/builds/1.0.9/rc2/">here</link>. 
            Please help us prepare for the official release by testing and providing feedback.  If you think you have found a 
            bug, please report it <link href="http://issues.apache.org/jira/secure/BrowseProject.jspa?id=10600">here</link>.
        </p>
    </section>	
    <section>
        <title>February 24, 2005 - MyFaces is Hot</title>
        <note label="David Geary (JSF Author and Creator of Tiles) Blogs on MyFaces">
            MyFaces is Hot<br/><br/>
            Disclaimer: From now on, we're going to have nothing but fun here!<br/><br/>
            I like to keep my finger on the pulse as much as I can so that I can track Big Things and Next Big Things. 
            One of the best ways to do that is to join mailing lists and watch how much traffic appears in your inbox. 
            Lately, I've taken notice of the traffic on the MyFaces mailing list, which seems to be running neck and 
            neck with the Struts developer's mailing list, which means that MyFaces is generating a lot of attention.
            <br/><br/>
            What? Oh no, I haven't joined the Ruby on Rails mailing list yet. 8-)
            <br/><br/>
            In the early days of JSF (last year), there was very little JSF traction. I think people were suspicious 
            of anything of that complexity that came out of a JSR, which in general is probably wise, but in this case, 
            of course, totally unfounded.
            <br/><br/>
            But lately, I'm seeing quite a surge in interest in JSF. And now that MyFaces is under the Apache umbrella, 
            I expect big things for it. Kudos to all the folks who have put in so much time and effort for MyFaces, such 
            as Heath Borders, Matthias Wessendorf, and Sean Schofield (Sean: how the heck can you be in so many places 
            at once?). Apologies to those I didn't mention; this list is off the top of my head.       
            <br/><br/>            
        </note>
        <p>Click <link href="http://www.jroller.com/page/dgeary/20050224#myfaces_is_hot">here</link> to read David Geary's blog.</p>
    </section>	        
    <section>
        <title>February 23, 2005 - MyFaces is Now a Top Level Apache Project</title>
        <note label="Email to myfaces-dev from ASF Board">
            Hi All,<br/>
            <br/>
            Congratulations to all for officially making MyFaces into a top level Apache
            project!
            <br/><br/>
            For the last couple of years, I believe the project has come a long way from
            its small beginnings. All of this is thanks to the contribution of every one
            of you, regardless of how large or small. Open source development, coupled
            with strong leadership (Manfred and others), is always a winning combination!
            <br/><br/>
            Once again, Congratulations.
            <br/><br/>
            Anton
        </note>
    </section>	    
    <section>
        <title>Resources</title>
        <p>If you are new to JavaServer Faces Technology look at the following resources to become familar with JSF:</p>
        <ul>
            <li><link href="http://www.jsfcentral.com/">JSFCentral</link></li>
            <li><link href="http://www.jamesholmes.com/JavaServerFaces/">James Holmes' JSF Resources</link></li>
        </ul>
    </section>
    
  </body>
</document>
